Parag Salbarde

UI/UX Designer

parag.salbarde@gmail.com

7 +91 7276 007 787

New Swastik Nagar, Amravati, Maharashtra, India - 444607

Social Media

LinkedIn/paraagsalbarde Behance/paraagsalbarde Medium/@parag.salbarde Instagram/bindokparaag

Language

English HIndi [Mother Tongue]

Hobbies

Sketching Painting Cooking

Summary

7+ years of corporate experience as a Product UX Designer with a variety of projects from Retail, ECommerce, ERP and SaaS. Skilled Engineer and passionate designer, specialised in UI/UX design and development of engaging interactions.

Skills

- Interface Design
- Wireframing
- High-fidelity Mockups
- Design System
- Interaction Design
- Prototyping
- UX Writing
- Responsive Web App
- User Research
- User Flow
- User Journey Map
- Usability Testing

Tools

- Adobe Illustrator
- AxureRP Pro 10
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma

- Autodesk Sketchbook
- Adobe XD

UI Development Skills And Tools

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- VS Code
- Bootstrap
- NodeJS, Git
- React Angular Material
- Agile Development

Experience

UX Designer at Capgemini India Pvt. Ltd. - *Mumbai*

July 2018 - Present

- Designing products for various industries, including SaaS, information design, API management, chatbots, etc.
- Leading UX co-creation sessions with the product owner and developer using a problem-solving methodology
- Collaborating with PMs for SaaS products and gather/evaluated improvements as per user and business requirements
- UI development using several IDEs such as VS Code, Eclipse, IntelliJ, etc.

UX Designer at Ril Jio Infocomm Ltd. - Mumbai

Nov 2016 - June 2018

- Worked on products in the fields of Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP), telecom customer acquisition, enterprise internet networks, etc.
- Analysis and synthesis of requirements in collaboration with management for the project's scope and seamless design experiences through UX Journeys.
- Supervision and support to development team on design execution
- Using Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe Photoshop, high fidelity design prototypes were produced.

UI/UX Designer at Ril Jio Infocomm Ltd. - Mumbai

Mar 2015 - Oct 2016

[Consultant from KloudData]

- Design of retail products like Point-of-sale(POS) and digital touchpoint for product's business.
- Agile Deployment of Designs at the MVP stage and thorough user testing and redesign sessions with a team of developers and designers.
- UI Design mobile apps by following hardware platform specific design guidelines like windows, IOS, Android.
- Driving development and communication of clear design guidelines, libraries and assets

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology Amravati University, Amravati [Maharashtra] - India **JUL 2014**